(wistful soul music)
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
(wistful soul music continues)
(melodic whistling)
♪ Do do do do, do do do ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Baby, baby ♪
♪ Do do do do, do do do ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Baby, oh yeah ♪
♪ I need a lover to give me ♪
♪ The kind of love that
would last always ♪
♪ I need somebody uplifting ♪
♪ To take me away, babe ♪
♪ Oh yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I want a lover who knows me, yeah ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Who understands how I feel inside ♪
♪ Someone to comfort and hold me ♪
♪ Through the long lonely nights ♪
♪ 'Til the dawn ♪
♪ Why don't you take me away ♪
♪ Dream lover come rescue me ♪
♪ Take me up take me down ♪
♪ Take me anywhere you want to baby now ♪
♪ I need you so desperately ♪
♪ Won't you please come around ♪
♪ 'Cause I wanna share
forever with you baby ♪
♪ Do do do do, do do do ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ With you, baby ♪
♪ I don't want another pretender, no ♪
♪ To disillusion me one more time ♪
♪ Whispering words of forever ♪
♪ Playing with my mind ♪
♪ No no, no no no, no no baby ♪
♪ I need someone to hold on to ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ The kind of love that won't fly away ♪
♪ I just want someone to belong to ♪
♪ Everyday of my life, always ♪
♪ So come and take me away ♪
♪ Dream lover come rescue me ♪
♪ Take me up take me down ♪
♪ Take me anywhere you want to baby now ♪
♪ I need you so desperately ♪
♪ Won't you please come around ♪
♪ 'Cause I wanna share
forever with you baby ♪
♪ With you ♪
♪ Do do do do, do do do ♪
(melodic whistling)
♪ Do do do do, yeah ♪
♪ Do do do do, do do do ♪
♪ Baby come and take me away ♪
♪ Dream lover come rescue me ♪
♪ Take me up take me down ♪
♪ Take me anywhere you want to baby now ♪
♪ I need you so desperately ♪
♪ Won't you please come around ♪
♪ 'Cause I wanna share
forever with you baby ♪
(melodic whistling)
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Do ba do ba do, do do do ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, ooh ♪
♪ Dream lover come rescue me ♪
♪ Take me up take me down ♪
♪ Take me anywhere you want to baby now ♪
♪ I need you so desperately ♪
♪ Won't you please come around ♪
♪ 'Cause I wanna share
forever with you baby ♪
(music ends)